Md Faisal Hossain

Cumilla District, Chattogram, Bangladesh



hello.faisalhossain@outlook.com



linkedin.com/in/mdfaisalhossain1



01814366774



https://web-faisal.github.io/profile/

Summary

Hi, This is Faisal. I am a Programmer & I am from Bangladesh. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (programming Language), JavaScript (programming Language), HTML(Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), SCSS(Senior Citizens Savings Scheme), Bootstrap (framework), React (framework), Node Js, git, bash, GitHub, Unity (game engine), Filmora X, logo Making, video editing & Microsoft office.

Experience



Programmer

NETIZEN IT LIMITED

Jan 2022 - Present (1 month +)

- · Coding is the best way to have fun.
- · You can create any type of program with coding.

Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department Of UK

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

- Maintained databases, mailing lists, telephone networks, and other information to facilitate functioning of health education programs.
- Compiled [Timeframe] budget reports, financial spreadsheets and organizational charts to support business operations and improve office organization.

Game Developer

Unity

Dec 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

- You can create any kind of game with unity
- Develop original content through social listening and independent sources.

Youtube Content Creator

YouTube

Dec 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Education



Adarsha Pre-Cadet School, Gunabati

SSC

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • React.js • Node js • Bootstrap • JavaScript • HTML, CSS, SCSS • Git, Bash, Github • Unity (game engine) • MongoDB • FilmoraX, Canva & Microsoft Office